Font update log:

v1.004 August 6, 2019 - Slightly tweaked the lowercase 'a' (including the accents), the feminine ordinal indicator, lowercase ligature 'ae', lowercase eng and the letters with an ogonek as well, and again, I forgot to correct one of the Kanji!!!

v1.003 July 12, 2019 - Added some more Kanji, and I forgot to correct one of the Kanji characters!!!

v1.002 July 11, 2019 - Added some other Kanji, modified lowercase I with ogonek and replaced the borrowed numerals(ASCII and 2-byte) that were in Rounded M+ with the original ones.

v1.000 June 8, 2019 - Initial Release

